Guide to the Susan Hanson Collection
The Wittliff Collections
Susan Hanson Collection
1984-1992
The Wittliff Collections
Hanson, Susan, 1951-
SWWC.042
0.5 Linear Feet
1 boxes
This collection is comprised primarily of photocopies of newspaper articles written by Susan Hanson, staff writer for the San Marcos Daily Record.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised primarily of photocopies of newspaper articles written by Susan Hanson, staff writer for the San Marcos Daily Record. Many articles are accompanied by notes and brief correspondence from the subject of the articles. The Interviews series includes handwritten notes taken during telephone interviews; articles written from these notes appear in the Articles series.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Source of Acquisition
Gift of Susan Hanson, 1992.
Biographical Notes
Susan Hanson was a staff writer for the San Marcos Daily Record, a newspaper in San Marcos, Texas from 1982-1999. Her column covers arts and culture, including interviews with regional novelists, poets, screenwriters, as well as politics and environmental history. Hanson currently teaches in the English Department at Texas State University, and writes for a San Marcos weekly newspaper, The Chautauquan.
Women journalists; Hanson, Susan, 1951-; San Marcos Daily Record
- Interviews
  - Interviews (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Contents
    Albert, Susan
    Bechtol, Bill
    Boyd, Sheryl
    Crook, Elizabeth
    Dunn, Margaret
    Flowers, Betty Sue
    Holland, Dick
    Lighthouse, Terry
    Merwin, W.S.
    Ogden, Scott
    Price, Randall
    Renick, Oren
    Thompson, Dave
- Articles, 1984-1992, undated
  - 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6-8)
  - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9-13)
  - undated (Box 1, Folder 14)